{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawk&#039;s Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Japan was part of the Allied Powers during World War I.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The Battle of Trafalgar took place on October 23rd, 1805",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Nazi Germany surrendered on Harry Truman&#039;s birthday while he was president.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The weapon Clint Eastwood uses in &quot;Dirty Harry&quot; was a .44 Automag.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In the &quot;Kagerou Daze&quot; series, Shintaro Kisaragi is prominently shown with the color red.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The protagonist&#039;s names in &#039;Who&#039;s Afraid of Virginia Woolf&#039;, George and Martha, were derived from George Washington and his wife.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
}